<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent on Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/recent/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recent on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:53:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/recent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>B &amp; B</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bed-and-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:53:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bed-and-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Breakfast and banter Who&#39;s the ranter? Eggs Benedict Diet not strict? Stop talking about dead mice It&#39;s really not nice Stories of road kill A tale to thrill! Definetely right To be dining room polite Watch what you say During the communal start to the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:35:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/football/</guid>
      <description>If ifs and ands were&amp;hellip;.. The actions that caused a stir Out on the green it ain&#39;t bowls A pitch is for scoring goals Place your bet For several in the net Chants and cheers Derision loud and angry jeers. Come on give it a rest The players did their best Rerun chatter, banter abounds As the folks leave the grounds Always a mission To move to the next division.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward Midnight</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/toward-midnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 11:08:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/toward-midnight/</guid>
      <description>The fire dances in the centre Circled by the painted caravans Wooden wagons embrace Voices rise and fall Sparks flurry before they fall She nods to those who notice Feet treading the dewy grass Dogs curled beneath steps Ignore her lantern&#39;s glow Above floors creak and windows glow A breeze riffles the flags The Big Top&#39;s only stirring Owl hoots approval As the circus prepares to sleep Strongman snoring; rumbling sleep Bareback ballerina&#39;s horse Crops meadow grass Snowy unicorn white Solid in the moonlight Mane shimmers by moonlight On the riverbank She hangs her clothes Upon outstretched branch Wades into the amber water Floats in the flowing water Swimming by the swans serene The river&#39;s their stage for grace Scars tingle a reminder She accepts her beauty within Doubt ebbs away, contentment within Willows trail the surface From the shadows she emerges Stands modestly statuesque Let&#39;s her skin dry naturally The stars see her naturally Drifting back to the fire She takes her place Beside the few that dally This a travelling community Now her close knit community Embers fade with kisses &amp;lsquo;Goodnight&amp;rsquo; Acts left in the sawdust ring She strokes the piebald by her tent Breaths this restful moment Foresees the next dream moment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring at Pulloxhill</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/spring-at-pulloxhill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 13:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/spring-at-pulloxhill/</guid>
      <description>A day after persistent rain. Spring sun the garden&#39;s gain. Clearing beds revealing green Locating plants yet unseen. Gladioli bulbs, orange and pink. I put them where I think, The path will be their catwalk. Each bold statement blooming stalk. We know the hurt war has cast. Make it stop! Please let if be the past. The news breaks our hearts. Still Spring uplifts and starts. Robin opportunistically near, Reminder of those held dear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If I had a wood of my own</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/if-i-had-a-wood-of-my-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 15:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/if-i-had-a-wood-of-my-own/</guid>
      <description>I would&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;. Plant my oak saplings Wildwood edge it Native trees Flowers for bees Green tunnel to lead you in With reclaimed stone Build a folly Mystic and mossy Create a dewpond In a clearing Where wild animals roam Wish for a &amp;lsquo;Wood Wide Web&amp;rsquo; Of fungi to spread Long for birds To sculpt their nests An area to coppice A place to rest Stand a Green Man there Alive with dappled light Symbolising the wisdom Of a holistic woodland idyll</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>