<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Misc on Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Misc on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 16:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancelled wedding day</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/cancelled-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 16:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/cancelled-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>Cancelled Wedding Day Sorry it was your special day Only when a reminder pinged did I say ”Oh it was supposed to be Charlotte and Danielle’s wedding day” This year’s plan has gone But hey ho the sun shone I’ve planted seeds And pulled up weeds Didn’t get to put on my gladrags Dance away from handbags Hopefully you feel no resentment Rather blessed with happiness and contentment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Sea</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/at-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 17:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/at-sea/</guid>
      <description>Distress sealed in a bottle Grief cast out to sea Rolled, roiled, tumbled Returned to shore. It’s energy and strength Releases sea glass A smooth survivor Every piece unique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odd Handknits</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/odd-handknits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 17:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/odd-handknits/</guid>
      <description>A fascination born of Flicking through pattern folders Reading books on cafe shelves And browsing crafter’s stalls Why? I speculate A knitted lampshade Oh dust will gather there Cable knit leotard Chaffing despair Moss stitched magazine cover Beyond rational comprehension Draw the line at a thong If you struggle with your tension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Ninja Falconzord</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/white-ninja-falconzord/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 18:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/white-ninja-falconzord/</guid>
      <description>That coveted Christmas present Parents eager to please, their intent The wrapping paper cast aside Wrestled the zord from inside Impressive box, plastic cocoon Awe inspiring demonstration soon Crestfallen the realisation is quick Appealing to know what’s the trick The advertising lie It couldn’t really fly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Lockdown</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/our-lockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 18:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/our-lockdown/</guid>
      <description>Panicking consumers flock down Toilet roll stocks down Scottish Minister stepped down Donald Trump orange clown Education Unions melt down Pubs definitely shut down Say your prayers; kneel down Missed Thursday clap, noted down Please R just go down Then we can have a hoedown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of The Pure</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/out-of-the-pure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/out-of-the-pure/</guid>
      <description>Spilling out onto the street Hidden behind in shadow Better for a gaggle Clubbers playing it over Underworld, hands in the air Through your head Loved up, hyped up Not ready for yer bed Keep talking &amp;quot;Who’s walking?” Watch the sunrise From Arthur’s Seat A shove, a push, a gentle nudge Lounging on the hillside Drying sweat Disparate dialogue Chat, chat, chat Enough being clever Enough of that Stretch out, lie back Up ’til dawn The light greets us And weariness sweeps us Down the slope Friendly green kaleidoscope ”Ye off home” ”Aye great night” ”See yas all” Parting of the ways Smiles, waves, smiles Sunrise across the miles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dylan and Nelson</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dylan-and-nelson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dylan-and-nelson/</guid>
      <description>
Lad and dog snoozing Through dreamland cruising Heavy sighs, occassional twitch In somnolence not a glitch Peace and calm shared is best Winter naps luxury rest </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poetaster</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/poetaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 08:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/poetaster/</guid>
      <description>With the name of Sheena Cook Likened to a common crook A haunting spook Is it such a fluke? That you really dare To believe you could have a flair That you really dare To write poems of note Not if it’s Sheena Cook you wrote In order to bring to an end Hastily written words that could offend</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>