<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:53:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>B &amp; B</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bed-and-breakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:53:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bed-and-breakfast/</guid>
      <description>Breakfast and banter Who&#39;s the ranter? Eggs Benedict Diet not strict? Stop talking about dead mice It&#39;s really not nice Stories of road kill A tale to thrill! Definetely right To be dining room polite Watch what you say During the communal start to the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/football/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 15:35:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/football/</guid>
      <description>If ifs and ands were&amp;hellip;.. The actions that caused a stir Out on the green it ain&#39;t bowls A pitch is for scoring goals Place your bet For several in the net Chants and cheers Derision loud and angry jeers. Come on give it a rest The players did their best Rerun chatter, banter abounds As the folks leave the grounds Always a mission To move to the next division.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward Midnight</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/toward-midnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 11:08:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/toward-midnight/</guid>
      <description>The fire dances in the centre Circled by the painted caravans Wooden wagons embrace Voices rise and fall Sparks flurry before they fall She nods to those who notice Feet treading the dewy grass Dogs curled beneath steps Ignore her lantern&#39;s glow Above floors creak and windows glow A breeze riffles the flags The Big Top&#39;s only stirring Owl hoots approval As the circus prepares to sleep Strongman snoring; rumbling sleep Bareback ballerina&#39;s horse Crops meadow grass Snowy unicorn white Solid in the moonlight Mane shimmers by moonlight On the riverbank She hangs her clothes Upon outstretched branch Wades into the amber water Floats in the flowing water Swimming by the swans serene The river&#39;s their stage for grace Scars tingle a reminder She accepts her beauty within Doubt ebbs away, contentment within Willows trail the surface From the shadows she emerges Stands modestly statuesque Let&#39;s her skin dry naturally The stars see her naturally Drifting back to the fire She takes her place Beside the few that dally This a travelling community Now her close knit community Embers fade with kisses &amp;lsquo;Goodnight&amp;rsquo; Acts left in the sawdust ring She strokes the piebald by her tent Breaths this restful moment Foresees the next dream moment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring at Pulloxhill</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/spring-at-pulloxhill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 13:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/spring-at-pulloxhill/</guid>
      <description>A day after persistent rain. Spring sun the garden&#39;s gain. Clearing beds revealing green Locating plants yet unseen. Gladioli bulbs, orange and pink. I put them where I think, The path will be their catwalk. Each bold statement blooming stalk. We know the hurt war has cast. Make it stop! Please let if be the past. The news breaks our hearts. Still Spring uplifts and starts. Robin opportunistically near, Reminder of those held dear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If I had a wood of my own</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/if-i-had-a-wood-of-my-own/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 15:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/if-i-had-a-wood-of-my-own/</guid>
      <description>I would&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;. Plant my oak saplings Wildwood edge it Native trees Flowers for bees Green tunnel to lead you in With reclaimed stone Build a folly Mystic and mossy Create a dewpond In a clearing Where wild animals roam Wish for a &amp;lsquo;Wood Wide Web&amp;rsquo; Of fungi to spread Long for birds To sculpt their nests An area to coppice A place to rest Stand a Green Man there Alive with dappled light Symbolising the wisdom Of a holistic woodland idyll</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kitchen Wish</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/kitchen-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 10:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/kitchen-wish/</guid>
      <description>Every hour on the hour I&#39;m gonna kiss a cauliflower Then I sigh and frown Still not garlicky cauli hash brown Pleading, wheedling &amp;ldquo;Please, Please&amp;rdquo; An indulgent triple cauliflower cheese&amp;rdquo; But stolidly it will remain A pale brassically brain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derbyshire Details</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/derbyshire-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/derbyshire-details/</guid>
      <description>A steadiness as that river flows Tree colours natural heraldry Swimming swagger of trout River festival of ducks, geese, gulls The sky a blue canvas Clouds roil in a temporary grey Cattle graze a placid Autumn And we walk through it Feeling gratitude for the grandeur</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be a bam just take a dram</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/whisky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/whisky/</guid>
      <description>bam - someone who is foolish, disruptive, annoying, obnoxious slàinte mhath - (pronounced Slanj-a-va) cheers dram - a small drink of whisky Aye it’s deemed Scotland’s national drink Afore you consume stop and think A wee nightcap before ya bed Relaxes and slows a busy head Just one for the road and ya’ll go Into the night with a cosy glow Try not to despise The advice of the “worldly wise” Clutching the bottle to your chest Ignoring what’s for the best When peer pressure’s stalking It’ll be the drink doin the talking Remember the amber liquid’s charm Is known to unleash untold harm Very few are protected from the spell Casting loved ones into living hell Stevenson wrote of Jekyll and Hyde Perhaps the demonic whisky slide A measure to raise a toast Ne’er suited to excessive boast The best malts require celebration Refined and savoured in moderation Be admired for who you are Only one generous “Slainte mhath”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Blackbirds</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</guid>
      <description>Even on the dampest day
Blackbirds cheerily play
Tail fans and chatter
Gather for a natter
Filling bare trees
Flutter and tease
Blackbirds style
It makes us smile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docwra’s Manor</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/docwras-manor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 07:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/docwras-manor/</guid>
      <description>Following the paths meander Carpets of snowdrops nod To their fellow hellebores Shy crocuses, cheery aconites Euphorbias delighted backdrop Proud orchard trees impress A solitary medlar on a branch Sinous trees reach out Mulberry wisely signifies nature Invokes our faith in nature too Mediterranean courtyard on a February day Grateful to be the sole visitors Time for reflection and introspection Looking at the details everywhere Honesty amongst the pots, the beds and barns Greenhouse a haven of warmth Inhale the comforting scents Succulents the hidden hermits As geraniums slumber in terracotta Propagation and hibernation&#39;s lair The gardens gently nurtured Self seeding encouraged; an informality Blooms the bountiful gifts That walls last to embrace And protect so much beauty within The Ravens who created here Were insightful and reflective Along with their loyal gardeners There is honour in what is shared Attuned to horticultural heraldry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowdrops</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/snowdrops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 08:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/snowdrops/</guid>
      <description>Apricity - feeling the sun’s warmth in winter. I loved this word and it falls alongside this poem Confident huddles Frosted foreground In the lee of hedges Purity nodding Come Spring! Come Spring!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January Morning</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/january-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 08:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/january-morning/</guid>
      <description>Sun and frost cast Mist rises on a scene Hedges screen Fields of winter barley My misguided longing For the simplicity of Working the land I run with history That of natural beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dry January</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</guid>
      <description>Why try? Why try to be dry? What might occur? A social slur Whining for wine A vodkaless void All things fizzy Make you dizzy Don’t really care for alcopops Always taste of sugary slops Avoid ruthless piratical rum No making merry with sherry Life feels queer Without beer Whistfully wishing for whisky Gin a major sin Acting with glee Faced with herbal tea Fortified by water Filling us with cheer The challenge of staying clear Of any percentage proof Might make us appear Sensible and aloof Please don’t judge When we try To get through January dry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine Fellows</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 08:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</guid>
      <description>Ground frost Makes digging slow Robin watches as I go Beady eyes Bare branch vantage Uncovered habitat advantage Flutters to earth Feeds in the wake Of spades thunk and quake Bold observer Jauntily tilted head Gratefully well fed Gardener&#39;s friends In winter’s fading light Robins brings us bright</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Macbeth/The Lady’s Flush</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</guid>
      <description>Forsooth, perhaps, or strewth. A glimmer of truth. Were the words of a witch? Trigger for a power crazed bitch. All that nocturnal wandering. Suggested she was pondering. Her and the thane’s wrongdoing. A miasma of guilt brewing. Rambling about the damned spot. Menopausal, sweaty and hot. The misguided onus on ambition. Resulting in insomnia and contrition. And there be the truth. Lady Macbeth just long in the tooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn at Pulloxhill</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/autumn-at-pulloxhill/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 09:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/autumn-at-pulloxhill/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin transformed to a mushy blob, On completion of it’s fearsome job. Cosmos sentinel below a tree. White flowers natural purity. Silent kite floats suspended high. In the grey stillness of the sky. Raking, spreading compost around. Robin brazen on the ground. Then school noises rise, Lunchtime’s whoops and cries. Watch more leaves flutter down. Only warrant a momentary frown. Empty mugs perched on the wall. Gratefully we’d emptied them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raking Leaves</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/raking-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 10:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/raking-leaves/</guid>
      <description>Trees slumber. Leaves dress the drive. Damp and dank, Tannins leach brown. Stretch and rake, Rake and gather. Piles grow. Slow……slow…… The next season, Settling in your heart. Satisfaction in effort, That rooks applaud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goths in pedalloes</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/goths-in-pedalloes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/goths-in-pedalloes/</guid>
      <description>Here goes Toward the pedalloes Clothes black as night An unexpected sight Wander through the park Collectively dark Under heavy fringes Adolescent twinges Of handsome faces Are definite traces Kohl rimmed eyes Loosened parental ties Payment taken Reserve shaken Languildy pedalling Heavy soled treddling Relax a while Share a smile Tending to be introspective Now in a social collective Perspectives are broader Gathered atop the water</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barely Bitter Betty Buttercup</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/betty-buttercup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/betty-buttercup/</guid>
      <description>There is a reason and story behind this but it is disguised here in a tale. One of those that is as old as time I am sure.
Barely Bitter Betty Buttercup Sent to work for Farmer Barleymow Her mother made a show. Betty was earning a honest day’s pay. Back when she didn’t have much to say. The farmer’s first wife died of consumption. In hindsight locals had a presumption; Barleymow’s eagerness to produce an heir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bees</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 16:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bees/</guid>
      <description>
If it was nae for the bees Where would we be? Bloody hungry! And there’d be nae honey </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancelled wedding day</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/cancelled-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 16:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/cancelled-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>Cancelled Wedding Day Sorry it was your special day Only when a reminder pinged did I say ”Oh it was supposed to be Charlotte and Danielle’s wedding day” This year’s plan has gone But hey ho the sun shone I’ve planted seeds And pulled up weeds Didn’t get to put on my gladrags Dance away from handbags Hopefully you feel no resentment Rather blessed with happiness and contentment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrapment</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 07:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</guid>
      <description>Trapped in a gilet Looking like a Hooray I borrowed it to keep warm Now my face is red It’s hotter than my bed The zip is dodgy My frame looks podgy Trapped in a gilet Hardly a crisis siutation On release a tiny celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bramble Patch</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bramble-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bramble-patch/</guid>
      <description>Avoided, unsightly Fearsome thorns that tear. Stop and consider. Listen to birdsong Heralding security within. An insectivorous city Retreat for modest mammals. Gallery of the spider’s webs, Enhanced by crystal dew. Pastel papery flowers. Nectar gatherers buzz, or flutter on elegant wings. A thriving natural community. Self sufficient relinquisher of black pearled berries. We will gratefully share. Appreciate that blackberry thicket For just being there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Sea</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/at-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 17:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/at-sea/</guid>
      <description>Distress sealed in a bottle Grief cast out to sea Rolled, roiled, tumbled Returned to shore. It’s energy and strength Releases sea glass A smooth survivor Every piece unique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puffin</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/puffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/puffin/</guid>
      <description>Puffin, puffin You look aloof Until you toddle off a cliff Giving off a fishy whiff. Puffin, puffin Do you have a chuffin? I will nae lie You cannae fly Puffin, puffin You are akin to A short stumpy penguin Kinda cute in a dinner suit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl on a Post</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/owl-on-a-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/owl-on-a-post/</guid>
      <description>Bright dawn A silent sentinel On a gate post Staring perfection Bringer of truth Open my eyes To nature’s calm You rise transient Fly shafts of light And gone. Two years on Spiritual stare I question why Maybe always there At peace, serene Wildly wise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odd Handknits</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/odd-handknits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 17:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/odd-handknits/</guid>
      <description>A fascination born of Flicking through pattern folders Reading books on cafe shelves And browsing crafter’s stalls Why? I speculate A knitted lampshade Oh dust will gather there Cable knit leotard Chaffing despair Moss stitched magazine cover Beyond rational comprehension Draw the line at a thong If you struggle with your tension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tideline</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</guid>
      <description>I sent my friend a linocut card Bird Watching by Diana Ashdown. And this is the poem I wrote On a mudflat somewhere Will be an oystercatcher Blissfully unaware Of an onlooker’s envious stare A bird whose life is clearly black and white Then whether the moon full and bright Tides will keep on turning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Ninja Falconzord</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/white-ninja-falconzord/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 18:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/white-ninja-falconzord/</guid>
      <description>That coveted Christmas present Parents eager to please, their intent The wrapping paper cast aside Wrestled the zord from inside Impressive box, plastic cocoon Awe inspiring demonstration soon Crestfallen the realisation is quick Appealing to know what’s the trick The advertising lie It couldn’t really fly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woodland and Forest</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/woodland-and-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 18:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/woodland-and-forest/</guid>
      <description>
And in a forest I shall find The wild in me And that nature is my soul </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Lockdown</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/our-lockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 18:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/our-lockdown/</guid>
      <description>Panicking consumers flock down Toilet roll stocks down Scottish Minister stepped down Donald Trump orange clown Education Unions melt down Pubs definitely shut down Say your prayers; kneel down Missed Thursday clap, noted down Please R just go down Then we can have a hoedown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light and Shadows</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/light-and-shadow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 18:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/light-and-shadow/</guid>
      <description>Light casting shadows If I were clever enough to to recreate The patterns that add a new dimension Dappling through a window The sun through a trees fluttering leaves Beauty in simplicity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down the Wye</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/down-the-wye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/down-the-wye/</guid>
      <description>A canoe on a river We’re the ballast Easy motion Paddles slice water Pewter translucence Rocks soft yellow green Weeds tendril stream We proceed with rhythm:by Swans indifferently serene Kingfisher’s electric flash Reflective purling stretches Momentarily hastens progress Towards Symonds Yat And with regret we leave A river&#39;s, sinous steady grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ode to a unicorn</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/ode-to-a-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 13:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/ode-to-a-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>We never knew your true name Just used you for a pool game When Martin ripped your insides out The young Watsons let out a shout Once proud and hugely inflated Now askew and flaccidly deflated Sheena will carry you gently away To the municipal bin area today No glittery spellbinding protection Enabling plastic fantasy unicorn resurrection</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeking celebrities in Ibiza (SCIIng)</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/seeking-celebrities-in-ibiza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 12:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/seeking-celebrities-in-ibiza/</guid>
      <description>A new quest created in jest As once he was King Arthur And has a famous father Sorry Finlay found fault With facts about flamingoes and salt Of course there&#39;s nothing wrong Conversing with those who choose a thong In an exclusive beach bar Wearing designer trunks, be a star If all else fails follow the rainbow bridge Noting biscuits should be stored in the fridge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out of The Pure</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/out-of-the-pure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/out-of-the-pure/</guid>
      <description>Spilling out onto the street Hidden behind in shadow Better for a gaggle Clubbers playing it over Underworld, hands in the air Through your head Loved up, hyped up Not ready for yer bed Keep talking &amp;quot;Who’s walking?” Watch the sunrise From Arthur’s Seat A shove, a push, a gentle nudge Lounging on the hillside Drying sweat Disparate dialogue Chat, chat, chat Enough being clever Enough of that Stretch out, lie back Up ’til dawn The light greets us And weariness sweeps us Down the slope Friendly green kaleidoscope ”Ye off home” ”Aye great night” ”See yas all” Parting of the ways Smiles, waves, smiles Sunrise across the miles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gin Tasting</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/gin-tasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 18:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/gin-tasting/</guid>
      <description>Let’s put a spin on the merits of gin Seemingly bananas won’t make you thin A ‘slimmers’ delight, tonic and gin If you’re an athlete set to win Not after a night sobbing into gin Victorian palaces rife with sin Never, ever throw gin in the bin Alcohol with berries thrown in Hey I’m referrin To head spin, give us more gin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dylan and Nelson</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dylan-and-nelson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dylan-and-nelson/</guid>
      <description>
Lad and dog snoozing Through dreamland cruising Heavy sighs, occassional twitch In somnolence not a glitch Peace and calm shared is best Winter naps luxury rest </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phallusology</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/phallusology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/phallusology/</guid>
      <description>Phalluses appear everywhere As if conjured from thin air Knobbly penis shaped potatoes A cucumber lying between tomatoes Children’s drawing. What’s that supposed to be? Not that wee fellow designed to go pee pee Graffiti overzealously crude Snowfield defiled to shock a rambling prude So next time you find yourself suffering from a shock When some advertising symbol resembles a large cock Realise you won’t be alone In thinking that’s not a bone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunrise, Sunset</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/sunrise-sunset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 18:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/sunrise-sunset/</guid>
      <description>
Who decides which is best? One stirs you from your rest The other reminds, lest we forget Relaxation ready to cast it’s net </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour of Dance</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/an-hour-of-dance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 18:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/an-hour-of-dance/</guid>
      <description>Light feet, big movements Amazing physicality Fascinating fun Children’s honest laughter A jumble of sale of clothes Tweed to the tempo Sprightly sparkles Rainbow rhythms Fulfilled by ingenuity Leaving the studio Drunk on creativity ’Happy Hour’ smiles</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In memory of....</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/in-memory-of/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 19:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/in-memory-of/</guid>
      <description>
Autumn Leaves fall around me Like memories they drift A deep rooted love Nothing will shift And strong I remain In remembrance of you </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Man’s Medley</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/modern-mans-medley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 08:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/modern-mans-medley/</guid>
      <description>I was tired of looking shady, my hair was too long Like a dislillusioned hippy with a favourite bong So while I lay there sleepin’, I had a dream in my head I was on the front page of a paper I’d recently read &amp;quot;f you hear this man singing, quickly exit the train If you’re not into yoga, if you have half a brain If you like making love at midnight after a game of Runescape Then no amount of cocktails will help you escape” I no longer felt shady, I felt renewed and rather keen But surfin and jet skiing ain’t part of my normal routine So I reinvented myself to look like a younger lad I’m not really a rapper but wrote something not bad Yes, I like playing Peggy and singing on the train I’m not much into health food, I am into champagne I’ve go to groove it out until tomorrow and create a soundscape At a bar on the high street we’ll plan our escape So I waited with high hopes and she walked in the place I knew her smile in an instant, the teeth with a brace It was a strangely blue lady and she said “Oh it’s you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Bakewell Basics</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bakewell-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 18:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bakewell-basics/</guid>
      <description>Sherry and nuts Tartan blanket Show ring dash Ducks on the river Make a splash Sunny days Chatting on the grass Derbyshire strolls Nothing flash Bakewell basic best We deserve the rest</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poetaster</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/poetaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 08:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/poetaster/</guid>
      <description>With the name of Sheena Cook Likened to a common crook A haunting spook Is it such a fluke? That you really dare To believe you could have a flair That you really dare To write poems of note Not if it’s Sheena Cook you wrote In order to bring to an end Hastily written words that could offend</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tide Flowing Fast</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tide-flowing-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2016 09:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tide-flowing-fast/</guid>
      <description>The current is swift, Boats and buoys await Their inevitable settling Onto mud shaped by the tide&#39;s pull. Seagull squawks, rides the current. Transition bewteen one tranquil scene Into the next: beached boats and navy pools. We watch transfixed yet not surprised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Whisker!!</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/what-a-whisker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 08:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/what-a-whisker/</guid>
      <description>When attending a less than exhilarating course To stay focused requires concentration of superhuman force My fingers will begin to wander across my facial skin Inevitably discovering a wiry whisker protruding from my chin Then my train of thought begins to meander To colleagues possible comments and slander ”Oh have you seen that bearded woman?” Never heeding facial depilation is positively subhuman Trying to pluck it out with stumpy fingernails Strong and defiant, of course that fails Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Holiday Monday</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bank-holiday-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 08:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bank-holiday-monday/</guid>
      <description>The day was grey I ran and it was windy Then we headed out to walk And we talked The green corn swished Cows and horse grazed A hawk hovered Nothing much was bothered In our passing by Still the clouds covered the sky. Sitting in a pub with pale ale A tin mug of pork scratchings An excited couple from London Visitors keen to chat This and that The beer, the building Next an elaborate woman in red Sat with a man sho spoke on his phone Of grouting tiles, smoking Sterling King Size She ate giant marshmallows Drank coffee and her name was Debbie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Walk</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/winter-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2015 09:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/winter-walk/</guid>
      <description>Dark hedgerows where scarlet berries hang Robins who stop to meet your eye Flocks of birds soaring high Pushing the clouds to reveal blue sky And as you walk many a mile Remember there’s been much that made you smile Two dogs hurtle by Proven loyalty makes you sigh A realisation in this open space Family and friends are yours to embrace</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology Chaos Theory</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/technology-chaos-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2015 19:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/technology-chaos-theory/</guid>
      <description>Social media Communal hysteria Misinterpreted texting Cringeworthy sexting Phone know your place! This is my mind space Facebook stalking No time for walking All that’s Twitter Makes me jitter Technology chaos theory Some think me dreary True friends look you in the eye Virtual ones can lie, lie, lie Make time for reality In a tech free principality</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Special</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/be-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 19:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/be-special/</guid>
      <description>Find it within to be special To do it once a day is fine Most of the day it’s good A week of your speciality Well that would be spectacular Settle for special once in a while And special is what you’ll become</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nay way Nigella</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/nae-way-nigella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 22:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/nae-way-nigella/</guid>
      <description>Nay way Nigella Nay way is swede sexy It’s solid n pale Ye canna pretend Seductive nay way Bottom of the scale Dress it up wi carrot Still the heavens will nae shift The only stirrings, oooooh……. The building gases From a rotund root Gauranteed to make ya toot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ever wondered?</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/ever-wondered/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2014 19:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/ever-wondered/</guid>
      <description>It seems only fair To tell someone they look like someone else If you think they do Why? Well because it could alter your perspective You just might treat them differently Sub consciously imagining Traces of that other being inhabiting their very essence It might not occur to them Or will it? That is the reason your are telling them They could be flattered Confused or down right irritated Always depends on how they think And they will think like the individual they are Rest assured they won’t be who you want them to be But hopefully they are just who they are And looks aside You embrace them in their entirety</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Spot</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/my-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/my-spot/</guid>
      <description>A spot that came to stay I was firm and endeavoured to chase it away Then it was like it moved in next door And became more difficult to ignore Your must admire it’s tenacity Whilst from friends came only pity I now fear more will come and join it A red, festive, glowing zit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonder where our place is</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/wonder-where-our-place-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2002 08:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/wonder-where-our-place-is/</guid>
      <description>As I read and toss in my bed Grey skies fill me with a longing for sun My mind wanders across the span Of all of those memories and reasons For the things I have done Nothing is more apparent than my slightness In the whole scheme of the world Therefore it is with warmth I cling to the love of those I love For I know full well there are those Who have known love at a price The smallest happenings can bring The wonder which helps us forget Hurts and sadness Let yourself stop to enjoy them As they can be caught in a suns ray Only in the passing of time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving On</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/moving-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 1989 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/moving-on/</guid>
      <description>His belongings sat in the hall Close to the door Everything fitted snugly into his boxes Expensive black and chrome gear Up to date PC and state of the art sculpture His coffee grinder and her toaster Her belongings strewn around the bedroom Some in boxes, some in bags Bits and pieces, memories he’d called junk Things they’d collected on the beach Heaps of clothes bought to impress Slowly wrapping mugs in paper She stared at a crossword he’d completed The cat softly rubbed against her leg Her cat now, she started to cry With a tea towel she dried her face And carefully avoided a swollen black eye</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>