<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>musings on Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/musings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in musings on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:50:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/musings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tideline</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</guid>
      <description>I sent my friend a linocut card Bird Watching by Diana Ashdown. And this is the poem I wrote On a mudflat somewhere Will be an oystercatcher Blissfully unaware Of an onlooker’s envious stare A bird whose life is clearly black and white Then whether the moon full and bright Tides will keep on turning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light and Shadows</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/light-and-shadow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 18:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/light-and-shadow/</guid>
      <description>Light casting shadows If I were clever enough to to recreate The patterns that add a new dimension Dappling through a window The sun through a trees fluttering leaves Beauty in simplicity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Holiday Monday</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bank-holiday-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 08:56:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bank-holiday-monday/</guid>
      <description>The day was grey I ran and it was windy Then we headed out to walk And we talked The green corn swished Cows and horse grazed A hawk hovered Nothing much was bothered In our passing by Still the clouds covered the sky. Sitting in a pub with pale ale A tin mug of pork scratchings An excited couple from London Visitors keen to chat This and that The beer, the building Next an elaborate woman in red Sat with a man sho spoke on his phone Of grouting tiles, smoking Sterling King Size She ate giant marshmallows Drank coffee and her name was Debbie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonder where our place is</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/wonder-where-our-place-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2002 08:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/wonder-where-our-place-is/</guid>
      <description>As I read and toss in my bed Grey skies fill me with a longing for sun My mind wanders across the span Of all of those memories and reasons For the things I have done Nothing is more apparent than my slightness In the whole scheme of the world Therefore it is with warmth I cling to the love of those I love For I know full well there are those Who have known love at a price The smallest happenings can bring The wonder which helps us forget Hurts and sadness Let yourself stop to enjoy them As they can be caught in a suns ray Only in the passing of time</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>