<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 07:57:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrapment</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 07:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</guid>
      <description>Trapped in a gilet Looking like a Hooray I borrowed it to keep warm Now my face is red it’s hotter than my bed The zip is dodgy My frame looks podgy Trapped in a gilet Hardly a crisis siutation On release a tiny celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be a bam just take a dram</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/whisky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/whisky/</guid>
      <description>bam - someone who is foolish, disruptive, annoying, obnoxious slàinte mhath - (pronounced Slanj-a-va) cheers dram - a small drink of whisky Aye it’s deemed Scotland’s national drink Afore you consume stop and think A wee nightcap before ya bed Relaxes and slows a busy head Just one for the road and ya’ll go Into the night with a cosy glow Try not to despise The advice of the “worldly wise” Clutching the bottle to your chest Ignoring what’s for the best When peer pressure’s stalking It’ll be the drink doin the talking Remember the amber liquid’s charm Is known to unleash untold harm Very few are protected from the spell Casting loved ones inot living hell Stevenson wrote of Jekyll and Hyde Perhaps the demonic whisky slide A measure to raise a toast Ne’er suited to excessive boast The best malts require celebration Refined and savoured in moderation Be admired for who you are Only one generous “Slainte mhath”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Blackbirds</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</guid>
      <description>Even on the dampest day
Blackbirds cheerily play
Tail fans and chatter
Gather for a natter
Filling bare trees
Flutter and tease
Blackbirds style
It makes us smile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docwra’s Manor</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/docwras-manor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 07:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/docwras-manor/</guid>
      <description>
Following the paths meander Carpets of snowdrops nod To their fellow hellebores Shy crocuses, cheery aconites Euphorbias delighted backdrop Proud orchard trees impress A solitary medlar on abranch Sinous trees reach out Mulberry wisely signifies nature Invokes our faith in nature too Mediterranean courtyard on a February day Grateful to be the sole visitors Time for reflection and introspection Looking at the details everywhere Honesty amongst the pots, the beds and barns Greenhouse a haven of warmth Inhale the comnforting scents Succulents the hidden hermits AS geraniums slumber in terracotta Propagation and hibernations lair The gardens gently nurtured Self seeding encouraged; an informality Blooms the bountiful gifts That walls last to embrace And protect so much beauty within The Ravens who created here Were insihgtful and reflective Along with their loyal gardeners There is honour in what is shared Attuned to horticultural heraldry </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowdrops</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/snowdrops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 08:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/snowdrops/</guid>
      <description>Apricity - feeling the sun’s warmth in winter. I loved this word and it falls alongside this poem Confident huddles Frosted foreground In the lee of hedges Purity nodding Come Spring Come Spring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January Morning</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/january-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 08:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/january-morning/</guid>
      <description>Sun and frost cast Mist rises on a scene Hedges screen Fields of winter barley My misguided longing For the simplicity of Working the land I run with history That of natural beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dry January</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</guid>
      <description>Why try? Why try to be dry? What might occur? A social slur Whining for wine A vodkaless void All things ifzzy Make you dizzy Don’t really care for alcopops Always taste of sugary slops Avoid ruthless piratical rum&amp;lt; No making merry with sherry Life feels queer Without beer Whistfully wishing for whisky Gin a major sin Acting with glee Faced with herbal tea Fortified by water Filling us with cheer The challneg of staying clear Of any percentage proof Might make us appear Sensible and aloof Please don’t judge When we try To get through January dry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine Fellows</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 08:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</guid>
      <description>Ground frost Makes digging slow Robin watches as I go Beady eyes Bare branch vantage Uncovered habitat advantage Flutters to earth Feeds in the wake Of spades thunk and quake Bold observer Jauntily tilted head Gratefully well fed Gardener&#39;s friends In winter’s fading light Robins brings us bright</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Macbeth/The Lady’s Flush</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</guid>
      <description>Forsooth, perhaps, or strewth. A glimmer of truth. Were the words of a witch? Trigger for a power crazed bitch. All that nocturnal wandering. Suggested she was pondering. Her and the thane’s wrongdoing. A miasma of guilt brewing. Rambling about the damned spot. Menopausal, sweaty and hot. The misguided onus on ambition. Resulting in insomnia and contrition. And there be the truth. Lady Macbeth just long in the tooth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>