<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 07:57:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrapment</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 07:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</guid>
      <description>Trapped in a gilet Looking like a Hooray I borrowed it to keep warm Now my face is red It’s hotter than my bed The zip is dodgy My frame looks podgy Trapped in a gilet Hardly a crisis siutation On release a tiny celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be a bam just take a dram</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/whisky/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 08:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/whisky/</guid>
      <description>bam - someone who is foolish, disruptive, annoying, obnoxious slàinte mhath - (pronounced Slanj-a-va) cheers dram - a small drink of whisky Aye it’s deemed Scotland’s national drink Afore you consume stop and think A wee nightcap before ya bed Relaxes and slows a busy head Just one for the road and ya’ll go Into the night with a cosy glow Try not to despise The advice of the “worldly wise” Clutching the bottle to your chest Ignoring what’s for the best When peer pressure’s stalking It’ll be the drink doin the talking Remember the amber liquid’s charm Is known to unleash untold harm Very few are protected from the spell Casting loved ones into living hell Stevenson wrote of Jekyll and Hyde Perhaps the demonic whisky slide A measure to raise a toast Ne’er suited to excessive boast The best malts require celebration Refined and savoured in moderation Be admired for who you are Only one generous “Slainte mhath”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Blackbirds</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</guid>
      <description>Even on the dampest day
Blackbirds cheerily play
Tail fans and chatter
Gather for a natter
Filling bare trees
Flutter and tease
Blackbirds style
It makes us smile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docwra’s Manor</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/docwras-manor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 07:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/docwras-manor/</guid>
      <description>Following the paths meander Carpets of snowdrops nod To their fellow hellebores Shy crocuses, cheery aconites Euphorbias delighted backdrop Proud orchard trees impress A solitary medlar on a branch Sinous trees reach out Mulberry wisely signifies nature Invokes our faith in nature too Mediterranean courtyard on a February day Grateful to be the sole visitors Time for reflection and introspection Looking at the details everywhere Honesty amongst the pots, the beds and barns Greenhouse a haven of warmth Inhale the comforting scents Succulents the hidden hermits AS geraniums slumber in terracotta Propagation and hibernation&#39;s lair The gardens gently nurtured Self seeding encouraged; an informality Blooms the bountiful gifts That walls last to embrace And protect so much beauty within The Ravens who created here Were insightful and reflective Along with their loyal gardeners There is honour in what is shared Attuned to horticultural heraldry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowdrops</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/snowdrops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 08:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/snowdrops/</guid>
      <description>Apricity - feeling the sun’s warmth in winter. I loved this word and it falls alongside this poem Confident huddles Frosted foreground In the lee of hedges Purity nodding Come Spring! Come Spring!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January Morning</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/january-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 08:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/january-morning/</guid>
      <description>Sun and frost cast Mist rises on a scene Hedges screen Fields of winter barley My misguided longing For the simplicity of Working the land I run with history That of natural beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dry January</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</guid>
      <description>Why try? Why try to be dry? What might occur? A social slur Whining for wine A vodkaless void All things fizzy Make you dizzy Don’t really care for alcopops Always taste of sugary slops Avoid ruthless piratical rum No making merry with sherry Life feels queer Without beer Whistfully wishing for whisky Gin a major sin Acting with glee Faced with herbal tea Fortified by water Filling us with cheer The challenge of staying clear Of any percentage proof Might make us appear Sensible and aloof Please don’t judge When we try To get through January dry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine Fellows</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 08:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</guid>
      <description>Ground frost Makes digging slow Robin watches as I go Beady eyes Bare branch vantage Uncovered habitat advantage Flutters to earth Feeds in the wake Of spades thunk and quake Bold observer Jauntily tilted head Gratefully well fed Gardener&#39;s friends In winter’s fading light Robins brings us bright</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Macbeth/The Lady’s Flush</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</guid>
      <description>Forsooth, perhaps, or strewth. A glimmer of truth. Were the words of a witch? Trigger for a power crazed bitch. All that nocturnal wandering. Suggested she was pondering. Her and the thane’s wrongdoing. A miasma of guilt brewing. Rambling about the damned spot. Menopausal, sweaty and hot. The misguided onus on ambition. Resulting in insomnia and contrition. And there be the truth. Lady Macbeth just long in the tooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autumn at Pulloxhill</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/autumn-at-pulloxhill/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 09:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/autumn-at-pulloxhill/</guid>
      <description>Pumpkin transformed to a mushy blob, On completion of it’s fearsome job. Cosmos sentinel below a tree. White flowers natural purity. Silent kite floats suspended high. In the grey stillness of the sky. Raking, spreading compost around. Robin brazen on the ground. Then school noises rise, Lunchtime’s whoops and cries. Watch more leaves flutter down. Only warrant a momentary frown. Empty mugs perched on the wall. Gratefully we’d emptied them all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raking Leaves</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/raking-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 10:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/raking-leaves/</guid>
      <description>Trees slumber. Leaves dress the drive. Damp and dank, Tannins leach brown. Stretch and rake, Rake and gather. Piles grow. Slow……slow…… The next season, Settling in your heart. Satisfaction in effort, That rooks applaud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goths in pedalloes</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/goths-in-pedalloes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/goths-in-pedalloes/</guid>
      <description>Here goes Toward the pedalloes Clothes black as night An unexpected sight Wander through the park Collectively dark Under heavy fringes Adolescent twinges Of handsome faces Are definite traces Kohl rimmed eyes Loosened parental ties Payment taken Reserve shaken Languildy pedalling Heavy soled treddling Relax a while Share a smile Tending to be introspective Now in a social collective Perspectives are broader Gathered atop the water</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barely Bitter Betty Buttercup</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/betty-buttercup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/betty-buttercup/</guid>
      <description>There is a reason and story behind this but it is disguised here in a tale. One of those that is as old as time I am sure.
Barely Bitter Betty Buttercup Sent to work for Farmer Barleymow Her mother made a show. Betty was earning a honest day’s pay. Back when she didn’t have much to say. The farmer’s first wife died of consumption. In hindsight locals had a presumption; Barleymow’s eagerness to produce an heir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bees</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 16:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bees/</guid>
      <description>If it was nae for the bees Where would we be? Bloody hungry! And there’d be nae honey</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancelled wedding day</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/cancelled-wedding-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 16:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/cancelled-wedding-day/</guid>
      <description>Cancelled Wedding Day Sorry it was your special day Only when a reminder pinged did I say ”Oh it was supposed to be Charlotte and Danielle’s wedding day” This year’s plan has gone But hey ho the sun shone I’ve planted seeds And pulled up weeds Didn’t get to put on my gladrags Dance away from handbags Hopefully you feel no resentment Rather blessed with happiness and contentment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bramble Patch</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bramble-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bramble-patch/</guid>
      <description>Avoided, unsightly Fearsome thorns that tear. Stop and consider. Listen to birdsong Heralding security within. An insectivorous city Retreat for modest mammals. Gallery of the spider’s webs, Enhanced by crystal dew. Pastel papery flowers. Nectar gatherers buzz, or flutter on elegant wings. A thriving natural community. Self sufficient relinquisher of black pearled berries. We will gratefully share. Appreciate that blackberry thicket For just being there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At Sea</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/at-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 17:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/at-sea/</guid>
      <description>Distress sealed in a bottle Grief cast out to sea Rolled, roiled, tumbled Returned to shore. It’s energy and strength Releases sea glass A smooth survivor Every piece unique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puffin</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/puffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/puffin/</guid>
      <description>Puffin, puffin You look aloof Until you toddle off a cliff Giving off a fishy whiff. Puffin, puffin Do you have a chuffin? I will nae lie You cannae fly Puffin, puffin You are akin to A short stumpy penguin Kinda cute in a dinner suit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl on a Post</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/owl-on-a-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/owl-on-a-post/</guid>
      <description>Bright dawn A silent sentinel On a gate post Staring perfection Bringer of truth Open my eyes To nature’s calm You rise transient Fly shafts of light And gone. Two years on Spiritual stare I question why Maybe always there At peace, serene Wildly wise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odd Handknits</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/odd-handknits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 17:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/odd-handknits/</guid>
      <description>A fascination born of Flicking through pattern folders Reading books on cafe shelves And browsing crafter’s stalls Why? I speculate A knitted lampshade Oh dust will gather there Cable knit leotard Chaffing despair Moss stitched magazine cover Beyond rational comprehension Draw the line at a thong If you struggle with your tension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tideline</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</guid>
      <description>I sent my friend a linocut card Bird Watching by Diana Ashdown. And this is the poem I wrote On a mudflat somewhere Will be an oystercatcher Blissfully unaware Of an onlooker’s envious stare A bird whose life is clearly black and white Then whether the moon full and bright Tides will keep on turning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Ninja Falconzord</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/white-ninja-falconzord/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 18:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/white-ninja-falconzord/</guid>
      <description>That coveted Christmas present Parents eager to please, their intent The wrapping paper cast aside Wrestled the zord from inside Impressive box, plastic cocoon Awe inspiring demonstration soon Crestfallen the realisation is quick Appealing to know what’s the trick The advertising lie It couldn’t really fly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woodland and Forest</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/woodland-and-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 18:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/woodland-and-forest/</guid>
      <description>And in a forest I shall find The wild in me And that nature is my soul</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>