<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humour on Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/humour/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humour on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:39:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/categories/humour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dry January</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/dry-january/</guid>
      <description>Why try? Why try to be dry? What might occur? A social slur Whining for wine A vodkaless void All things fizzy Make you dizzy Don’t really care for alcopops Always taste of sugary slops Avoid ruthless piratical rum No making merry with sherry Life feels queer Without beer Whistfully wishing for whisky Gin a major sin Acting with glee Faced with herbal tea Fortified by water Filling us with cheer The challenge of staying clear Of any percentage proof Might make us appear Sensible and aloof Please don’t judge When we try To get through January dry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lady Macbeth/The Lady’s Flush</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 09:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/the-ladys-flush/</guid>
      <description>Forsooth, perhaps, or strewth. A glimmer of truth. Were the words of a witch? Trigger for a power crazed bitch. All that nocturnal wandering. Suggested she was pondering. Her and the thane’s wrongdoing. A miasma of guilt brewing. Rambling about the damned spot. Menopausal, sweaty and hot. The misguided onus on ambition. Resulting in insomnia and contrition. And there be the truth. Lady Macbeth just long in the tooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goths in pedalloes</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/goths-in-pedalloes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/goths-in-pedalloes/</guid>
      <description>Here goes Toward the pedalloes Clothes black as night An unexpected sight Wander through the park Collectively dark Under heavy fringes Adolescent twinges Of handsome faces Are definite traces Kohl rimmed eyes Loosened parental ties Payment taken Reserve shaken Languildy pedalling Heavy soled treddling Relax a while Share a smile Tending to be introspective Now in a social collective Perspectives are broader Gathered atop the water</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barely Bitter Betty Buttercup</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/betty-buttercup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/betty-buttercup/</guid>
      <description>There is a reason and story behind this but it is disguised here in a tale. One of those that is as old as time I am sure.
Barely Bitter Betty Buttercup Sent to work for Farmer Barleymow Her mother made a show. Betty was earning a honest day’s pay. Back when she didn’t have much to say. The farmer’s first wife died of consumption. In hindsight locals had a presumption; Barleymow’s eagerness to produce an heir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrapment</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 07:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/entrapment/</guid>
      <description>Trapped in a gilet Looking like a Hooray I borrowed it to keep warm Now my face is red It’s hotter than my bed The zip is dodgy My frame looks podgy Trapped in a gilet Hardly a crisis siutation On release a tiny celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gin Tasting</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/gin-tasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 18:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/gin-tasting/</guid>
      <description>Let’s put a spin on the merits of gin Seemingly bananas won’t make you thin A ‘slimmers’ delight, tonic and gin If you’re an athlete set to win Not after a night sobbing into gin Victorian palaces rife with sin Never, ever throw gin in the bin Alcohol with berries thrown in Hey I’m referrin To head spin, give us more gin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phallusology</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/phallusology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/phallusology/</guid>
      <description>Phalluses appear everywhere As if conjured from thin air Knobbly penis shaped potatoes A cucumber lying between tomatoes Children’s drawing. What’s that supposed to be? Not that wee fellow designed to go pee pee Graffiti overzealously crude Snowfield defiled to shock a rambling prude So next time you find yourself suffering from a shock When some advertising symbol resembles a large cock Realise you won’t be alone In thinking that’s not a bone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Man’s Medley</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/modern-mans-medley/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 08:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/modern-mans-medley/</guid>
      <description>I was tired of looking shady, my hair was too long Like a dislillusioned hippy with a favourite bong So while I lay there sleepin’, I had a dream in my head I was on the front page of a paper I’d recently read &amp;quot;f you hear this man singing, quickly exit the train If you’re not into yoga, if you have half a brain If you like making love at midnight after a game of Runescape Then no amount of cocktails will help you escape” I no longer felt shady, I felt renewed and rather keen But surfin and jet skiing ain’t part of my normal routine So I reinvented myself to look like a younger lad I’m not really a rapper but wrote something not bad Yes, I like playing Peggy and singing on the train I’m not much into health food, I am into champagne I’ve go to groove it out until tomorrow and create a soundscape At a bar on the high street we’ll plan our escape So I waited with high hopes and she walked in the place I knew her smile in an instant, the teeth with a brace It was a strangely blue lady and she said “Oh it’s you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a Whisker!!</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/what-a-whisker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 08:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/what-a-whisker/</guid>
      <description>When attending a less than exhilarating course To stay focused requires concentration of superhuman force My fingers will begin to wander across my facial skin Inevitably discovering a wiry whisker protruding from my chin Then my train of thought begins to meander To colleagues possible comments and slander ”Oh have you seen that bearded woman?” Never heeding facial depilation is positively subhuman Trying to pluck it out with stumpy fingernails Strong and defiant, of course that fails Why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nay way Nigella</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/nae-way-nigella/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 22:58:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/nae-way-nigella/</guid>
      <description>Nay way Nigella Nay way is swede sexy It’s solid n pale Ye canna pretend Seductive nay way Bottom of the scale Dress it up wi carrot Still the heavens will nae shift The only stirrings, oooooh……. The building gases From a rotund root Gauranteed to make ya toot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Spot</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/my-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2013 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/my-spot/</guid>
      <description>A spot that came to stay I was firm and endeavoured to chase it away Then it was like it moved in next door And became more difficult to ignore Your must admire it’s tenacity Whilst from friends came only pity I now fear more will come and join it A red, festive, glowing zit</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>