<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>birds on Sheena Cook</title>
    <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/tags/birds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in birds on Sheena Cook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sheenacook.github.io/tags/birds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter Blackbirds</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/blackbirds/</guid>
      <description>Even on the dampest day
Blackbirds cheerily play
Tail fans and chatter
Gather for a natter
Filling bare trees
Flutter and tease
Blackbirds style
It makes us smile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine Fellows</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 08:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/fine-fellows/</guid>
      <description>Ground frost Makes digging slow Robin watches as I go Beady eyes Bare branch vantage Uncovered habitat advantage Flutters to earth Feeds in the wake Of spades thunk and quake Bold observer Jauntily tilted head Gratefully well fed Gardener&#39;s friends In winter’s fading light Robins brings us bright</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puffin</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/puffin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 17:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/puffin/</guid>
      <description>Puffin, puffin You look aloof Until you toddle off a cliff Giving off a fishy whiff. Puffin, puffin Do you have a chuffin? I will nae lie You cannae fly Puffin, puffin You are akin to A short stumpy penguin Kinda cute in a dinner suit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl on a Post</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/owl-on-a-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 17:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/owl-on-a-post/</guid>
      <description>Bright dawn A silent sentinel On a gate post Staring perfection Bringer of truth Open my eyes To nature’s calm You rise transient Fly shafts of light And gone. Two years on Spiritual stare I question why Maybe always there At peace, serene Wildly wise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tideline</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/tideline/</guid>
      <description>I sent my friend a linocut card Bird Watching by Diana Ashdown. And this is the poem I wrote On a mudflat somewhere Will be an oystercatcher Blissfully unaware Of an onlooker’s envious stare A bird whose life is clearly black and white Then whether the moon full and bright Tides will keep on turning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Down the Wye</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/down-the-wye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 17:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/down-the-wye/</guid>
      <description>A canoe on a river We’re the ballast Easy motion Paddles slice water Pewter translucence Rocks soft yellow green Weeds tendril stream We proceed with rhythm:by Swans indifferently serene Kingfisher’s electric flash Reflective purling stretches Momentarily hastens progress Towards Symonds Yat And with regret we leave A river&#39;s, sinous steady grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Bakewell Basics</title>
      <link>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bakewell-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 18:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sheenacook.github.io/post/bakewell-basics/</guid>
      <description>Sherry and nuts Tartan blanket Show ring dash Ducks on the river Make a splash Sunny days Chatting on the grass Derbyshire strolls Nothing flash Bakewell basic best We deserve the rest</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>